<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pyVmomi on Encore Technologies - DevOps Blog</title>
    <link>https://encoretechnologies.github.io/categories/pyvmomi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pyVmomi on Encore Technologies - DevOps Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://encoretechnologies.github.io/categories/pyvmomi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated addition of VMware VM to Host Affinity Rules</title>
      <link>https://encoretechnologies.github.io/blog/2019/01/vmware-affinity-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://encoretechnologies.github.io/blog/2019/01/vmware-affinity-rules/</guid>
      <description>Background VMware Affinity rules can solve many issues in a virtualized environment with out the need to create different clusters or datacenters to separate Virtual Machines. The specific need that we at Encore had for this was that when a vm is being cloned, if the VM was migrated to a different Host due to a vMotion, the custom spec with Kickstart files or Autounattended Syspreps would fail.
This was a random error that would only happened when vCenter or a host was overloaded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated addition of VMware Disks and Controllers</title>
      <link>https://encoretechnologies.github.io/blog/2017/10/vmware-disks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://encoretechnologies.github.io/blog/2017/10/vmware-disks/</guid>
      <description>When adding disks to VMware VM using Python we need to use the pyVmomi VMware SOAP API to communicate with vCenter. pyVmomi gives us a lot of very helpful features that take out a lot of the guess work in adding new disks to a VMware VM.
You can install pyVmomi from pip into a virtualenv like the following:
virtualenv ~/vmware source ~/vmware/bin/activate pip install pyvmomi  VMware Connection pyVmomi makes it really easy to connect to the VMware vCenter environment to query information and perform all the necessary tasks needed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>