<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nick Maludy on Encore Technologies - DevOps Blog</title>
    <link>https://encoretechnologies.github.io/categories/nick-maludy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nick Maludy on Encore Technologies - DevOps Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://encoretechnologies.github.io/categories/nick-maludy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing 2-Factor Auth For Workflows In StackStorm Using Inquiries</title>
      <link>https://encoretechnologies.github.io/blog/2017/10/stackstorm-inquiries/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://encoretechnologies.github.io/blog/2017/10/stackstorm-inquiries/</guid>
      <description>A common request i&amp;rsquo;ve seen on the StackStorm Slack Channel is the ability to utilize 2-factor auth before executing a workflow. Users sometimes have very powerful workflows that require extra care, or a second set of eyes before executing. Inquiries are an experimental feature in StackStorm 2.5 (changelog) that allow the workflow to pause and wait for input from a user before proceeding. In this post we&amp;rsquo;re going to use inquiries to secure a workflow execution using Duo 2-factor authentication (2FA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated creation of StackStorm Packs</title>
      <link>https://encoretechnologies.github.io/blog/2017/10/automated-creation-of-stackstorm-packs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://encoretechnologies.github.io/blog/2017/10/automated-creation-of-stackstorm-packs/</guid>
      <description>In StackStorm a pack is logical organization that contains related actions, aliases, policies, rules and sensors. To get a good overview of what a pack is please see the excellent StackStorm Pack documentation.
Most users of StackStorm wish to either integrate with a new system that&amp;rsquo;s not available in the Exchange or use StackStorm to execute custom automation scripts. The way to accomplish this is to create a new Pack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Blog</title>
      <link>https://encoretechnologies.github.io/blog/2017/09/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://encoretechnologies.github.io/blog/2017/09/intro/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Encore DevOps blog!
We on the DevOps team have been working for about a year and a half building tons of automation solutions for Encore&amp;rsquo;s Managed Services customers. Up until now we haven&amp;rsquo;t had a place to publicly showcase the more technical work that we&amp;rsquo;ve been doing. This blog serves as a new space for our engineers to share their experiences around new and innovating technologies we&amp;rsquo;re exploring.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>